<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
 <title type="text">My Blog: My Blog</title>
 <link rel="self" href="http://www.example.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" />
 <link href="http://www.example.com/index.html" />
 <id>urn:http-www-example-com:-index-html</id>
 <updated>2019-09-05T15:17:55Z</updated>
 <entry>
  <title type="text">Edgar's post</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.example.com/2019/09/edgar-s-post.html?utm_source=all&amp;utm_medium=Atom" />
  <id>urn:http-www-example-com:-2019-09-edgar-s-post-html</id>
  <published>2019-09-05T15:17:55Z</published>
  <updated>2019-09-05T15:17:55Z</updated>
  <author>
   <name>Edgar Cobos</name></author>
  <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;For Lab 1, first we formed a group of 4 and completed the Hello Computer excercise as a warm-up. As part of the warm-up, we had to start the VM, start a terminal and practice making a directory, creating a file in that directory, and cleaning up. Next, this time individiaully, I followed the Frog Tutorial from the course outline to create a frog project under the cs2613 directory I had just created. I also started the new blog page for this journal entry, removing the previous fake entry created by the frog setup command. Then, I refreshed the browser running raco flag -bp to make sure everything was working properly. Moreover, I read Section 1.3 from Pro Git and revised the fundamentals of version control with Git. This included learning about the three states that files can reside in: modified, staged, and commited, and the three main sections of a Git project: working directory, staging area and .git directory (repository). I created the Git repository and configured my name, email and the editor, used git add, to add the journal folder and then used git commit to run my Initial commit. In order to get some hints about writing good commit messages, I read the Commit Guidelines from 5.2 of Pro Git. Finally, I added the remote repository so that I can push this blog to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.example.com/2019/09/edgar-s-post.html?utm_source=all&amp;amp;utm_medium=Atom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;More&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</content></entry></feed>